

Le, Anh Dinh (Louis)

O London, ON N5V1W1
437 882 2778

louis.le.2307@gmail.com

PROFILES

www.linkedin.com/in/le-anh-dinh-021a3599

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Dedicated professional and Mobile Application Development student with eight (8) plus years successful experience working for international companies. I was promoted to Project Manager which allowed me to collect and develop more valuable experience managing and deploying projects.

Recognized for my skills and accomplishments, I was awarded the role of General Manager further encompassing my leadership and operations skills building a smoothly run international technical organization.

SKILLS

- Kotlin & Swift
- React Native
- JavaScript
- HTML & CSS
- MySQL & Firebase
- Client/server IT platform
- Enterprise Infrastructure
- Telecom VoIP
- Project Management
- Group Management

EDUCATION

Post-Graduated |

09/2021 - 12/2022

Mobile Application Development

Fanshawe College, London, ON

• GPA: 4.0 (Estimation)

Bachelor of Science |

Network and System Administration

Asia E University, Malaysia

GPA: 3.47

09/2009 - 07/2012

WORK HISTORY

GENERAL MANAGER

06/2020 to 04/2021

BRICKMATE | Vietnam, Ho Chi Minh City

- Managed and operated all activities of representative office in Vietnam
- Built core technical team (finance, HR and technical team leaders)
- Built internal systems which can support for developer and financial team
- Conducted for market researching and all marketing activities Build relationship with partners in local and oversea area
- Instructed and cooperated with Project manager to plan for each project
- Worked with QC team for building test plan of all products before releasing to clients
- Analyzed weekly reports from all departments (tech, finance and HR) and discussed with higher level for finding solution

 Established and administered annual budget with controls to prevent overages, minimize burn rate and support sustainability objectives

R&D AND PROJECT MANAGER

01/2018 to 05/2020

VHT | Vietnam, Ho Chi Minh City

- Managed Projects for big Telco in Vietnam and oversea countries
- Researched and deployed successfully the first project of Microsoft in Vietnam and other projects
- Had knowledge and experienced in Network and Telecom Infrastructure

APAC TECHNICAL PROJECT MANAGER

07/2016 to 12/2017

AARENET AG Switzerland APAC | Vietnam, Ho Chi Minh City

- Managed and deployed project for almost telephony providers in APAC area
- Worked closely with technical team from Switzerland for troubleshooting any issue from customer provided
- Worked closely with sale team as resale for advising technical solution
- Achieved experiences in Linux, VoIP, Soft-switch, Firewall (FortiGate, Iptables), Databases (my SQL), SIP devices, router and switch, DAML, Datacenter, Click-to-call, WebRTC, E1, basic SS7.

TI SITE MANAGER

01/2014 to 07/2016

ALLERGAN | Vietnam, Ho Chi Minh City

- Received and resolving issue from Vietnam' user and assisted foreign user to raise their issue on system
- Planned for developing new system of company
- Managed and ordering all IT equipment
- Processed and deployed for all local user's requirements

REWARD

Award For Excellence from Allergan company. 04/2015
 Dean's Honor Roll from Fanshawe college. 01/2022

Dean's Honor Roll from Fanshawe college.
 05/2022

HOBBIT

- Travelling
- Cooking
- Reading
- Researching